call
What did you see?
Is Crusade coming?
Do you often dream things that happen just as you dream them. Yes.
The test is simple.
Remove your hand from the box.
And you die.
functional box
pain
You inherit too much power.
You have proven you can rule yourself.
Now you must learn to rule others something none of your ancestors learned.
My father rules an entire planet, he's losing it.
He's getting a richer one.
He'll lose that.
Right. Iraqis is a death trap.
vacuum
This is an extermination.
Taking my family off one by one.
Let's fight my demons.
An animal called in a trap will nor off its own leg to escape.[ASR not working]
What will you do?
Legends will be born.
realization
Hello Duke.
For the fear is gone.
Only I will remain.