Welcome ESL students. I'm your guide for today. We're
going to analyze and empowering speech by the renowned actress and activist Emma Watson Emma
a native English speaker delivers this
speech with great eloquence her communication style Rich
vocabulary and grammar usage
provide an excellent learning platform for us. Are you ready to explore
and learn? Let's get started.
I was appointed
as Goodwill Ambassador
for un women's six months ago.
And The more I've spoken about
feminism. The more I have
realized that fighting for women's rights.
Has too often become synonymous. with
man hating
if there is one thing
I know for certain.
It is that this
has
to stop.
Emma Begins by sharing her experience as a Goodwill Ambassador for un women
notice the use of the past simple tense. I was
appointed which we use for completed actions
in the past. She also uses the conjunction and to
connect her ideas.
for the record feminism by
definition is the
belief that men and women should have equal
rights and opportunities.
It is the theory
of the political
economic and
social equality of the sexes.
In this segment Emma provides a clear definition of feminism
a term that is often misunderstood. The
term feminism is an example of a compound noun, which is a noun made up of
two or more words. In this case feminism is derived from female and
the suffix ism which indicates a practice system or
ideology. I started questioning gender-based assumptions a long time ago.
When I was eight.
I was confused being called bossy.
Because I
wanted to direct the plays that we would put on for our parents. But
the boys were
When at 14 I
started to be sexualized by certain elements of the media.
When it's 15,
my girlfriend started dropping out of their beloved sports teams.
Because they didn't want to appear
Emma shares her personal experiences using the past simple tense I started. This tense
is used for actions that began and ended in the
past. She also uses the conjunction when to introduce a specific time in the
past one at
18. My male
friends were unable to express their
I decided. That
I was a feminist.
And this seemed uncomplicated to me.
But my recent research
has shown
me. That feminism has become an unpopular word.
women
Are choosing
not
to identify
as feminist?
apparently
I am among the ranks of
women whose expressions are
seen as too strong.
too aggressive
isolating
and anti-men
unattractive even
Emma continues her personal experiences again using the conjunction when to introduce a
specific time in the past. She
also uses the phrase
I am
among which is a present tense phrase used to indicate inclusion
in a
group. Why has
the word
become such an uncomfortable one.
I am from Britain.
And I think it is
right that I am paid the same as my male counterparts.
I think it is right
that I should be able to make decisions about my own
body. I think it
is, right. That women be
involved on my behalf
in the policies and the decisions that will affect my life.
I think it is
right. That's socially
I am afforded the same respect as men.
Emma questions the discomfort around the term feminism
notice the use of the question word
why which we use to
ask for reasons? She also uses the present simple
tense. I think to
express her opinions,
but sadly. I
can say that there is no one country in the
world where all
women can expect to receive these rights.
No country in the world
can yet say
that they have achieved agenda equality.
Emma uses the conjunction
but
to introduce a contrasting point. She
also uses the modal verb can to talk about ability or possibility.
Modal verbs are a type of auxiliary verb that expressed necessity possibility permission or ability in this
case can
is used to express possibility indicating
that it's possible but not certain.
Thank you very
Emma ends her speech with a polite
expression. Thank you. Very
very much using polite phrases in English is important in maintaining a respectful
conversation. Congratulations Learners. We've
just analyzed Emma Watson's speech focusing on various grammatical elements, like verb tenses conjunctions and question words
along with enriching our vocabulary. Make sure to watch the full speech
and see if you can identify more of these elements. Don't forget to
subscribe to our newsletter and download our free ebooks for more resources. Continue your Learning
Journey by watching our other videos. See you next
time for another Deep dive into the world of English speeches.
Bye.